Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Isbell, Robert N. Col. (Box 36, Folder 1324)
  - Isham, Ralph Col. (Box 36, Folder 1324)
  - Isham, S. (Box 36, Folder 1324)
  - Israeli, Samuel Michael (Box 36, Folder 1324)
  - Ives, Brayton (Box 36, Folder 1325)
  - Ives, Eli (Box 36, Folder 1325)
  - Ives, Gerard Merrick (Box 36, Folder 1325)
  - Ives, Henry (Box 36, Folder 1326)
  - Ives, Irwin M. (Box 36, Folder 1326)
  - Ives, Wilbur (Box 36, Folder 1326)
  - Jack, Thomas McKinney (Box 36, Folder 1327)
  - Jackson, Arthur Forbes (Box 36, Folder 1327)
  - Jackson, Edith B. (Box 36, Folder 1327)
  - Jackson, George Edwards (Box 36, Folder 1328)
  - Jackson, Henry Rootes (Box 36, Folder 1328)
  - Jackson, Irvine Sinclair (Box 36, Folder 1328)
  - Jackson, Isaac Morton (Box 36, Folder 1329)
  - Jackson, James Caleb (Box 36, Folder 1329)
  - Jackson, Joseph Frederick Edward (Box 36, Folder 1329)
  - Jackson, Levi (Box 36, Folder 1330-31)
  - Jackson, Roderick C., Rev. (Box 36, Folder 1332)
  - Jacobs, Monroe S. (Box 36, Folder 1332)
  - Jaffray, Clive Palmer (Box 36, Folder 1332)
  - Jaffray, James Freeman (Box 36, Folder 1332)
  - Jaffray, Robert (Box 36, Folder 1333)
  - James, Arthur (Box 36, Folder 1334)
  - James, Fleming (Box 36, Folder 1334)
  - James, H. A. (Box 36, Folder 1334)
  - James, Henry Jr. (Box 36, Folder 1334)
  - James, Horace (Box 36, Folder 1335)
  - James, J. Edmund (Box 36, Folder 1335)
  - Jamison, Harold Burton (Box 36, Folder 1335)
  - Jamison, John Henry (Box 36, Folder 1336)
  - Janeway, Theodore Caldwell (Box 36, Folder 1336)
  - Jansen, Frederick Israel (Box 36, Folder 1337)
  - Jarboe, John Rudolph (Box 36, Folder 1337)
  - Jarman, John H., Jr. (Box 36, Folder 1337)
  - Jarvis, Abraham (Box 36, Folder 1338)
  - Jarvis, James Jackson (Box 36, Folder 1338)
  - Jarvis, Samuel Farmar (Box 36, Folder 1338)
  - Jarvis, William (Box 36, Folder 1339)
  - Jay, John (Box 36, Folder 1339)
  - Jay, William (Box 36, Folder 1339)
  - Jeffords, Walter M. (Box 36, Folder 1340)
  - Jeffras, ?? (Box 36, Folder 1340)
  - Jeme. Tien-Yow (Box 36, Folder 1341)
  - Jenkins, Allston (Box 36, Folder 1341)
  - Jenkins, Edward Hopkins (Box 36, Folder 1342)
  - Jenkins, Timothy L. (Box 36, Folder 1342)
  - Jenks, Arthur Edmands (Box 36, Folder 1342)
  - Jenks, Grove P. (Box 36, Folder 1343)
  - Jennings, Charles Buckley (Box 36, Folder 1343)
  - Jennings, John Joseph (Box 36, Folder 1343)
  - Jennings, Oliver Burr (Box 36, Folder 1344)
  - Jennings, Walter (Box 36, Folder 1344)
  - Jennings, Walter Barry (Box 36, Folder 1344)
  - Jepson, Prof. ?? (Box 36, Folder 1345)
  - Jernberg, Robert August (Box 36, Folder 1345)
  - Jerome, Edward Columbus (Box 36, Folder 1345)
  - Jerome, William T. (Box 36, Folder 1346)
  - Jerrems, Alexander Nicoll (Box 36, Folder 1346)
  - Jessup, Robert Johnson (Box 36, Folder 1346)
  - Jessup, Samuel (Box 36, Folder 1347)
  - Jessup, Stuart Dodge (Box 36, Folder 1347)
  - Jessup, William Henry (Box 36, Folder 1348)
  - Jessup, W. N. (Box 36, Folder 1348)
  - Jesup, Morris Ketchum (Box 36, Folder 1349)
  - Jewett, Josiah (Box 36, Folder 1349)
  - Jewett, McCormick (Box 36, Folder 1350)
  - Jewett, Paul Nathan (Box 36, Folder 1350)
  - Jewett, Raymond Smith (Box 36, Folder 1350)
  - Jocelyn, Nathaniel (Box 36, Folder 1351)
  - Johnes, Edward R. (1873) (Box 36, Folder 1351)
  - Johns, Hanson Atkins (Box 36, Folder 1351)
  - Johnson, Alexander (Box 36, Folder 1352)
  - Johnson, Alexander Bryan (Box 36, Folder 1352)
  - Johnson, Alvin S. (Box 36, Folder 1353)
  - Johnson, Birger L., Jr. (Box 36, Folder 1353)
  - Johnson, Charles Frederick (Box 36, Folder 1353)
  - Johnson, Crompton T. (Box 36, Folder 1354)
  - Johnson, Eino Algot (Box 36, Folder 1354)
  - Johnson, George A. (Box 36, Folder 1354)
  - Johnson, George Chrysler (Box 36, Folder 1355)
  - Johnson, Howard Robbins (Box 36, Folder 1355)
  - Johnson, James Weldon (Box 36, Folder 1355)
  - Johnson, John Wesley (Box 36, Folder 1355)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird (Box 36, Folder 1356)
  - Johnson, Lee Arthur (Box 36, Folder 1357)
  - Johnson, Leeds (Box 36, Folder 1357)
  - Johnson, Lorenzo Medici (Box 36, Folder 1357)
  - Johnson, Percy Lincoln (Box 36, Folder 1357)
  - Johnson, Philip and Paul Rudoph (Box 36, Folder 1357)
  - Johnson, R. H. (Box 36, Folder 1358)
  - Johnson, Rankin (Box 36, Folder 1358)
  - Johnson, Robert Clyde (Box 36, Folder 1358)
  - Johnson, Samuel (Box 36, Folder 1358)
  - Johnson, Samuel William (Box 36, Folder 1359-61)
  - Johnson, Thomas Robert (Box 36, Folder 1362)
  - Johnson, Treat Baldwin (1898S) (Box 36, Folder 1362)
  - Johnson, William Martin (Box 36, Folder 1362)
  - Johnson, William Samuel (Box 36, Folder 1363)
  - Johnson, William Woolsey (Box 36, Folder 1364)
  - Johnston, Colles (Box 36, Folder 1364)
  - Johnston, Francis Upton (Box 36, Folder 1364)
  - Johnston, George Brinton (Box 36, Folder 1365)
  - Johnston, Henry P. (Box 37, Folder 1366)
  - Johnston, J. Stoddard (Box 37, Folder 1366)
  - Johnston, Prof. John (Box 37, Folder 1366)
  - Johnston, John Jr. (Box 37, Folder 1367)
  - Johnston, Richard H. (Box 37, Folder 1367)
  - Johnston, William Preston (Box 37, Folder 1367)
  - Jones, Alexander (Box 37, Folder 1368)
  - Jones, Alfred Lee (Box 37, Folder 1368)
  - Jones, Arnold (Box 37, Folder 1368)
  - Jones, Arthur Russell (Box 37, Folder 1369)
  - Jones, Augustus Turner (Box 37, Folder 1369)
  - Jones, Daniel Albion (1884) (Box 37, Folder 1369)
  - Jones, Frank Hatch (Box 37, Folder 1369)
  - Jones, Frederick S. (Box 37, Folder 1370)
  - Jones, Frederick William, Jr. (Box 37, Folder 1371)
  - Jones, George (Box 37, Folder 1371)
  - Jones, Henry Webster (Box 37, Folder 1372)
  - Jones, Howard H. (Box 37, Folder 1372)
  - Jones, John A. W. (Box 37, Folder 1372)
  - Jones, Luther Maynard (Box 37, Folder 1373)
  - Jones, Marjory L. (Box 37, Folder 1373)
  - Jones, Paul (Box 37, Folder 1374)
  - Jones, Stanley Bayne (Box 37, Folder 1374)
  - Jones, Thomas Albert Dwight (Box 37, Folder 1374)
  - Jones, W. Clyde (Box 37, Folder 1375)
  - Jones, Frank Winthrop (Box 37, Folder 1375)
  - Jones, Ralph Edward (Box 37, Folder 1375)
  - Jones, Walter St. John (1873) (Box 37, Folder 1375)
  - Jones, William H. (Box 37, Folder 1375)
  - Jordan, Riverda Harding (Box 37, Folder 1376)
  - Jordan, William Wills (Box 37, Folder 1376)
  - Joy, James Richard (Box 37, Folder 1376)
  - Joyce, A.W. (Box 37, Folder 1377)
  - Joyce, Hewette Elwell (Box 37, Folder 1377)
  - Judd, A. Francis (Box 37, Folder 1378)
  - Judd, C. H. (Box 37, Folder 1378)
  - Judd, Charles H. (Box 37, Folder 1378)
  - Judd, Ethan Wood (Box 37, Folder 1378)
  - Judd, Sylvester (Box 37, Folder 1379)
  - Judson, Alexander C. (Box 37, Folder 1379)
  - Judson, Charles N. (Box 37, Folder 1379)
  - Judson, Ephraim (Box 37, Folder 1380)
  - Judson, Frederick Arthur (Box 37, Folder 1380)
  - Judson, Oliver B. (Box 37, Folder 1380)
  - Judson, Walter (Box 37, Folder 1381)
  - Julianelle, Lester A.J. (Box 37, Folder 1382)
  - Julin, Charles Edward (Box 37, Folder 1382)
  - Jussersand, [Jean Adriane Antoine] Jules (Box 37, Folder 1382)
  - Kabayama, Sukebida (Box 37, Folder 1382)
  - Kagawa, Rev. Toyahiko (Box 37, Folder 1382)
  - Kahn, Eugen (Box 37, Folder 1383)
  - Kahn, Louis (Box 37, Folder 1383)
  - Kahn, Reuben Leon (Box 37, Folder 1383)
  - Kai, Ernest (Box 37, Folder 1384)
  - Kaimer, Frederick Richard (Box 37, Folder 1384)
  - Kallman, William Loomis (Box 37, Folder 1384)
  - Kane, John Kintzing (Box 37, Folder 1385)
  - Karpinski, Louis C. (Box 37, Folder 1385)
  - Karrman, Henry Sebastian (Box 37, Folder 1386)
  - Kaulukou, Abraham Gilbert (Box 37, Folder 1386)
  - Kaynor, Warren F. (Box 37, Folder 1386)
  - Kazemzadeh, Firuz (Box 37, Folder 1387)
  - Keamy, Thomas (Box 37, Folder 1387)
  - Kean, John (Box 37, Folder 1388)
  - Kean, Julian Halsted (Box 37, Folder 1388)
  - Keating, William Pierson (Box 37, Folder 1388)
  - Keator, Frederic William (Box 37, Folder 1389)
  - Keator, John Frisbee (Box 37, Folder 1389)
  - Keck, Thomas A. (Box 37, Folder 1390)
  - Keeler, Ralph (Box 37, Folder 1390)
  - Keeler, Seneca McNeil (Box 37, Folder 1391)
  - Keenan, William P. (Box 37, Folder 1391)
  - Kefauver, Estes (Box 37, Folder 1392)
  - Keith, Walter Woodruff (Box 37, Folder 1392)
  - Keller, Adolf (Box 37, Folder 1392)
  - Keller, Albert Galloway (Box 37, Folder 1393)
  - Keller, Helen (Box 37, Folder 1393)
  - Keller, Phillip (?) (Box 37, Folder 1393)
  - Kelleter, Paul D. (Box 37, Folder 1393)
  - Kelley, Frank Benedict (Box 37, Folder 1394)
  - Kelley, Cilla Whitman (Box 37, Folder 1394)
  - Kelley, Evan W. (Box 37, Folder 1394)
  - Kelley, Lawrence Morgan (Box 37, Folder 1394)
  - Kelley, Robert (Box 37, Folder 1395)
  - Kellogg (Box 37, Folder 1395)
  - Kellogg, Chauncey Seymour (Box 37, Folder 1395)
  - Kellogg, David Hyde (Box 37, Folder 1396)
  - Kellogg, Francis Bartlett (Box 37, Folder 1396)
  - Kellogg, Frank Albert (Box 37, Folder 1397)
  - Kellogg, Fred William (Box 37, Folder 1397)
  - Kellogg, George Aaron (Box 37, Folder 1397)
  - Kellogg, Henry Jarvis (Box 37, Folder 1398)
  - Kellogg, Martin (Box 37, Folder 1399)
  - Kellogg, Remington (Box 37, Folder 1399)
  - Kellogg, Sanford Brown (Box 37, Folder 1399)
  - Kellogg, Stephen Wright (Box 37, Folder 1400)
  - Kelly, Colin P., Jr. (Box 37, Folder 1400)
  - Kelly, H. C. (Box 37, Folder 1400)
  - Kelly, Henry S. (Box 37, Folder 1401)
  - Kelvin, Lord (Box 37, Folder 1401)
  - Kelly, William (Box 37, Folder 1402)
  - Kelly, William C. (Box 37, Folder 1402)
  - Kelsey, Arthur J. (Box 38, Folder 1403)
  - Kelsey, C. H. (Box 38, Folder 1403)
  - Kelsey, Clarence, Dedication to Memorial (Box 38, Folder 1404)
  - Kelsey, John Reeve (Box 38, Folder 1405)
  - Kempton, Herbert Mayberry (Box 38, Folder 1405)
  - Kenan, William R. (Box 38, Folder 1405)
  - Kendall, William S. (Box 38, Folder 1405)
  - Kendrick, John B. (Box 38, Folder 1405)
  - Kensiton, Kenneth (Box 38, Folder 1406)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald (Box 38, Folder 1407-09)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P. Family (Box 38, Folder 1410)
  - Kennedy, M. C. (Box 38, Folder 1410)
  - Kennedy, Miles Coverdale (Box 38, Folder 1411)
  - Kennerley, Morley (Box 38, Folder 1411)
  - Kennett, Thomas A. (Box 38, Folder 1411)
  - Kent, Albert Emmett (Box 38, Folder 1412)
  - Kent, James (Box 38, Folder 1413-14)
  - Kent, William (Box 38, Folder 1415)
  - Kenyon Albert James (Box 38, Folder 1415)
  - Keogh, Andrew (Box 38, Folder 1416-18)
  - Keppelman, John Arthur (Box 38, Folder 1419)
  - Kernan, George A. (Box 38, Folder 1420)
  - Kernan, Thomas (Box 38, Folder 1420)
  - Kernochan, Francis Edward (Box 38, Folder 1421)
  - Kernochan, Joseph Frederic (Box 38, Folder 1421)
  - Kerr, Robert Bage (Box 38, Folder 1422)
  - Kesden, S. Samuel (Box 38, Folder 1422)
  - Kessen, William (Box 38, Folder 1423)
  - Ketcham, William P. (Box 38, Folder 1423)
  - Keyes, Edward L. (Box 38, Folder 1423)
  - Kidric, Boris (Box 38, Folder 1424)
  - Kilborne, Robert Stewart (Box 38, Folder 1425)
  - Kilbourne, Henry Wells (Box 38, Folder 1425)
  - Kilbourne, William S. (Box 38, Folder 1425)
  - Kilduff, Edw. J. (Box 38, Folder 1426)
  - Kilidjkale, Emin (Box 38, Folder 1426)
  - Killebrew, Robert S. (Box 38, Folder 1426)
  - Killinger, Charles Hittel (Box 38, Folder 1427)
  - Kilpatrick, John Reed (Box 38, Folder 1428)
  - Kimball, Chase (Box 38, Folder 1428)
  - Kimball, H. D. (Box 38, Folder 1429)
  - Kimball, James Hugh (Box 38, Folder 1429)
  - Kimball, John Edwin (Box 38, Folder 1430)
  - Kimball, Joseph S. (Box 38, Folder 1431)
  - Kimball, Thomas D. (Box 38, Folder 1431)
  - Kimball, Walter (Box 38, Folder 1432)
  - Kimberly, Clarke Oler (Box 38, Folder 1432)
  - Kimberly [Kimberley], W. R. (Box 38, Folder 1432)
  - Kimpton, H. H. (Box 38, Folder 1433)
  - Kimura, Shunkichi (Box 38, Folder 1433)
  - Kincaid, Carl (Box 38, Folder 1433)
  - King, Clarence (Box 38, Folder 1434)
  - King, Henry Lord Page (Box 38, Folder 1434)
  - King, Hiram M. (Box 38, Folder 1434)
  - King, John Hamilton (Box 38, Folder 1435)
  - King, R. F. (Box 38, Folder 1435)
  - King, Robert Snyder (Box 38, Folder 1435)
  - King, Stoddard (Box 38, Folder 1436)
  - King, William L. (Box 38, Folder 1436)
  - Kingsbury, Howard (1863) (Box 38, Folder 1437)
  - Kingsbury, Howard (1926) (Box 38, Folder 1438)
  - Kingsbury, Oliver Addison (Box 38, Folder 1438)
  - Kingsley, G. L. (Box 38, Folder 1438)
  - Kingsley, H. C. (Box 38, Folder 1439-40)
  - Kingsley, James Luce (Box 39, Folder 1441-43)
  - Kingsley, John M. (Box 39, Folder 1444)
  - Kingsley, William Lathrop (Box 39, Folder 1444)
  - Kingsley, Willy L. (Box 39, Folder 1444)
  - Kinney, John Coddington (Box 39, Folder 1445)
  - Kinney, Orson Alonzo (Box 39, Folder 1445)
  - Kinney, Ralph Parsons (Box 39, Folder 1445)
  - Kinney, Sarah [Wife of John Coddington Kinney, 1861] (Box 39, Folder 1446)
  - Kinney, Troy (and Margaret) (Box 39, Folder 1446)
  - Kiphuth, Robert J. H. (Box 39, Folder 1447-48)
  - Kirby, Ephraim (Box 39, Folder 1449)
  - Kirby, Thomas B. (Box 39, Folder 1449)
  - Kirtland, Edwin Leander (Box 39, Folder 1449)
  - Kitchel, Cornelius L. (Box 39, Folder 1450)
  - Kitchel, Harvey Dennison (Box 39, Folder 1451)
  - Kitchel, Harvey, Sheldon (Box 39, Folder 1451)
  - Kitchel, William Lloyd (Box 39, Folder 1451)
  - Kitchell, C.P. (Box 39, Folder 1452)
  - Kittredge, Albert R. (Box 39, Folder 1452)
  - Kittredge, Alfred Beard (Box 39, Folder 1453)
  - Kittredge, George Alvan (Box 39, Folder 1453)
  - Kleber, Herbert D. (Box 39, Folder 1454)
  - Klein, Harold L. (Box 39, Folder 1454)
  - Kleiner, Simon B. (Box 39, Folder 1455)
  - Kleppinger, Henry Stephen (Box 39, Folder 1456)
  - Kligermann, Sheff (Box 39, Folder 1456)
  - Kline, C. Mahlon (Box 39, Folder 1457)
  - Kline, George W. (Box 39, Folder 1458)
  - Knapp, D. R. (Box 39, Folder 1458)
  - Knapp, Wallace Percy (Box 39, Folder 1458)
  - Knapp, William Ireland (Box 39, Folder 1459)
  - Knapp, William Jared, Jr. (Box 39, Folder 1459)
  - Kneeland, Yale (Box 39, Folder 1460)
  - Kneller, George Frederick (Box 39, Folder 1460)
  - Knevals, Edward Weston (Box 39, Folder 1461)
  - Knevlas, Sherman W. (Box 39, Folder 1461)
  - Knight, ? (Box 39, Folder 1461)
  - Knight, Edward Vinton (Box 39, Folder 1462)
  - Knight, F. Irving (Box 39, Folder 1462)
  - Knight, Francis M. (Box 39, Folder 1462)
  - Knight, George Henry (Box 39, Folder 1463)
  - Knight, Howard R. (Box 39, Folder 1463)
  - Knight, Jonathan (Box 39, Folder 1464-65)
  - Knight, Newell Clark (Box 39, Folder 1466)
  - Knollenberg, Bernhard (Box 39, Folder 1466)
  - Knopf, Adolph (Box 39, Folder 1466)
  - Knowles, Donald T. (Box 39, Folder 1466)
  - Knowles, Ellis (Box 39, Folder 1467)
  - Knowles, George Gray (Box 39, Folder 1467)
  - Knox, H. S. (Box 39, Folder 1467)
  - Knox, J. A. (Box 39, Folder 1468)
  - Knox, Philander C. (Box 39, Folder 1468)
  - Knox, William Francis (Box 39, Folder 1468)
  - Kohler, Frederic D. (Box 39, Folder 1469)
  - Kohler, George Coburn (Box 39, Folder 1469)
  - Kohler, H. (Box 39, Folder 1470)
  - Kohler, J. (Box 39, Folder 1470)
  - Kohler, James P. (Box 39, Folder 1470)
  - Kohler, Walter Jodok, Jr. (Box 39, Folder 1471)
  - Koltesky, Harry (Box 39, Folder 1471)
  - Kollman, Bartholomew & Charles (Box 39, Folder 1471)
  - Komroff, Manuel (Box 39, Folder 1472)
  - Koo, Dr. T. Z. (Box 39, Folder 1472)
  - Koskoff, Mrs. Yale David (Box 39, Folder 1472)
  - Kountze, Augustus Frederick (Box 39, Folder 1473)
  - Kountze, Herman Davis (Box 39, Folder 1473)
  - Kovarik, Alois F. (Box 39, Folder 1473)
  - Kramer, Samuel (Box 39, Folder 1474)
  - Kramer, Simon (Box 39, Folder 1474)
  - Kreider, Albert (Box 39, Folder 1474)
  - Krevit, Benjamin (Box 39, Folder 1475)
  - Kruttschnitt, Julius, Jr. (Box 39, Folder 1475)
  - Kubie, Donald Albert (Box 39, Folder 1475)
  - Kubler, George Alexander (Box 39, Folder 1475)
  - Kuenzel, John G. (Box 39, Folder 1476)
  - Kumler, P. (Box 39, Folder 1476)
  - Kung, H. H. (Box 39, Folder 1476)
  - Kunitz, Stanley (Box 39, Folder 1476)
  - Kurie, Franz N. D. (Box 39, Folder 1477)
  - Kwei, Paul Chi-ting (Box 39, Folder 1477)
  - Lackland, Edgar Conrad (Box 39, Folder 1477)
  - Ladd, George Trumbull (Box 39, Folder 1478-79)
  - Laisun, Spencer Tsen (Box 39, Folder 1480)
  - Lake, Edgar Jay (Box 39, Folder 1480)
  - Lamar, Joseph R. (Box 39, Folder 1481)
  - Lambert, Alexander (Box 39, Folder 1481)
  - Lambert, Edward Wilberforce (Box 39, Folder 1481)
  - Lambert, L.B. (Box 39, Folder 1482)
  - Lambert, ?? (Box 39, Folder 1482)
  - Lamberton, William Buenler (Box 39, Folder 1482)
  - Lambie, William S. (Box 39, Folder 1483)
  - Lamdin, Charles R. (Box 39, Folder 1483)
  - Lamond, John K. (Box 39, Folder 1483)
  - Lampson, George (Box 40, Folder 1484)
  - Lampson, William (Box 40, Folder 1484)
  - Lamson, Edwin Ruthven (Box 40, Folder 1485)
  - Lamson, William Judson (Box 40, Folder 1485)
  - Landers, George Marcellus (Box 40, Folder 1485)
  - Landon, Edward Hunter (Box 40, Folder 1486)
  - Landon, Richard Wilcox (Box 40, Folder 1486)
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss (Box 40, Folder 1486)
  - Lane, Roger K. (Box 40, Folder 1487)
  - Lane, William Allen (Box 40, Folder 1487)
  - Lane, Wolcott Gibbs (Box 40, Folder 1488-89)
  - Lang, B. J. (Box 40, Folder 1490)
  - Lang, Henry R. (Box 40, Folder 1490)
  - Langdon, George Edward (Box 40, Folder 1490)
  - Langner, Siegfried (Box 40, Folder 1491)
  - Lanier, Albert (Box 40, Folder 1492)
  - Lanier, Henry, Jr. (Box 40, Folder 1492)
  - Lanier, James (Box 40, Folder 1492)
  - Lansing, Dirck Cornelius (Box 40, Folder 1493)
  - Lapham, H. G. (Box 40, Folder 1493)
  - Lapham, Walter Jerome (Box 40, Folder 1493)
  - Larkin, Charles L. (Box 40, Folder 1493)
  - Larned, William Augustus (Box 40, Folder 1494-95)
  - LaRoche, Chester J. (Box 40, Folder 1496)
  - Larson, C. Syrach (Box 40, Folder 1496)
  - Larson, Joshua (Box 40, Folder 1497)
  - Larus, John R. (Box 40, Folder 1497)
  - Lathrop, Joseph (Box 40, Folder 1497)
  - Latimer, Frederick P., Jr. (Box 40, Folder 1498)
  - Latting, Charles P. (1873) (Box 40, Folder 1498)
  - Laughlin, Irwin Boyle (Box 40, Folder 1498)
  - Law, Richard (Box 40, Folder 1498)
  - Lawrance, Charles Lanier (Box 40, Folder 1499)
  - Lawrance, Thomas Garner (Box 40, Folder 1499)
  - Lawrence, George (Box 40, Folder 1500)
  - Laws, H. Langdon (Box 40, Folder 1500)
  - Lawton, Sanford (Box 40, Folder 1500)
  - Lay, Beirne (Box 40, Folder 1501)
  - Laying, James Dawson, Jr. (Box 40, Folder 1501)
  - Leach, Francis Augustus (Box 40, Folder 1501)
  - Leaf, Edward Bowman (Box 40, Folder 1502)
  - Leal, John (Box 40, Folder 1502)
  - Lear, Henry (Box 40, Folder 1502)
  - Learned, Bela Peck (Box 40, Folder 1503)
  - Learned, Elmer T. (Box 40, Folder 1503)
  - Learned, William L. (Box 40, Folder 1503)
  - Leavens, Francis Jedidiah (Box 40, Folder 1504)
  - Leavenworth, Clifford Walter (Box 40, Folder 1504)
  - Leavitt, D. (Box 40, Folder 1505)
  - Leavitt, Joshua (Box 40, Folder 1505)
  - LeBlanc K. (Box 40, Folder 1505)
  - LeBourgeois, Joseph Charles (Box 40, Folder 1506)
  - LeBoutillier, Martin (Box 40, Folder 1506)
  - Ledeen, Theodore J. (Box 40, Folder 1506)
  - Ledig, Thomas F. (Box 40, Folder 1506)
  - Ledyard, Augustus Canfield (Box 40, Folder 1507)
  - Lee, Alfred M. (Box 40, Folder 1507)
  - Lee, Frank Theodosius (Box 40, Folder 1507)
  - Lee, J. W. (Box 40, Folder 1508)
  - Lee, Paul J. (Box 40, Folder 1508)
  - Lee, Richard C. (Box 40, Folder 1508)
  - Lee, Samuel Henry (Box 40, Folder 1509)
  - Lee, Yan-phou (Box 40, Folder 1510)
  - Leech, Malcolm Wallace (Box 40, Folder 1510)
  - Leeds, Charles Henry (Box 40, Folder 1510)
  - Leeds, Norman (Box 40, Folder 1511)
  - Leffingwell, William (Box 40, Folder 1511)
  - Legore, Harold W. (Box 40, Folder 1511)
  - Lehlbach, Frederick Reimold (Box 40, Folder 1512)
  - Lehman, L. H. (Box 40, Folder 1512)
  - Lehmann, R. C. (Box 40, Folder 1512)
  - Lehmer, Charles (Box 40, Folder 1513)
  - Lehrman, Lewis Edward (Box 40, Folder 1513)
  - Leighton, K. T. (Box 40, Folder 1514)
  - Leill, R. S. (Box 40, Folder 1514)
  - Lellwable, Carl G. (Box 40, Folder 1514)
  - Lemordant, Jean-Julien (Box 40, Folder 1514)
  - Leopold, Aldo (Box 40, Folder 1515)
  - Lerner, Max (Box 40, Folder 1515)
  - Levens, William Stephen (Box 41, Folder 1516)
  - Leverett, William Josiah (Box 41, Folder 1516)
  - Levering, E. W. (Box 41, Folder 1516)
  - Levermore, Charles Herbert (Box 41, Folder 1517)
  - Levison, Jacob J. (Box 41, Folder 1517)
  - Levy, William Maynard (Box 41, Folder 1517)
  - Lewis, Charles (Box 41, Folder 1517)
  - Lewis, Charles H. (Box 41, Folder 1518)
  - Lewis, Charlton (Box 41, Folder 1519-20)
  - Lewis, Eugene H. (Box 41, Folder 1521)
  - Lewis, Frank Bradley (Box 41, Folder 1521)
  - Lewis, G. F. (Box 41, Folder 1522)
  - Lewis, George E., Dr. (Box 41, Folder 1522)
  - Lewis, George Henry (Box 41, Folder 1522)
  - Lewis, Ira (Box 41, Folder 1523)
  - Lewis, John (Box 41, Folder 1523)
  - Lewis, S. G. (Box 41, Folder 1523)
  - Lewis, Sinclair (Box 41, Folder 1524-27)
  - Lewis, Tracy H. (Box 41, Folder 1528)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. (Box 41, Folder 1529)
  - Leyburn, James G. (Box 41, Folder 1530)
  - L"Hommedieu, Ezra (Box 41, Folder 1530)
  - Liang, Tun-Yen (Box 41, Folder 1530)
  - Libbey, Frank (Box 41, Folder 1531)
  - Liggett, Richard A. (Box 41, Folder 1531)
  - Lightner, Theodore Alexander (Box 41, Folder 1531)
  - Liles, Luther B. (Box 41, Folder 1532)
  - Lill, Edward R. (Box 41, Folder 1532)
  - Lilley, John Leavens (Box 41, Folder 1532)
  - Lilley, Theodore, Sr. (Box 41, Folder 1533)
  - Lilley, Theodore, Jr. (Box 41, Folder 1533)
  - Lillie, B [illegible] (Box 41, Folder 1533)
  - Limburger, Ernest Abraham (Box 41, Folder 1534)
  - Lincoln, James Oris (Box 41, Folder 1534)
  - Lindeman, Herman H. (Box 41, Folder 1534)
  - Lindenburg, Carl Robins (Box 41, Folder 1535)
  - Lindley, Daniel (Box 41, Folder 1535)
  - Lindsay, Peter McNair (Box 41, Folder 1536)
  - Lindsey, Charles A. (Box 41, Folder 1536)
  - Lines, Edwin Stevens (Box 41, Folder 1537)
  - Lines, Harold S. (Box 41, Folder 1538)
  - Linhart, George H. (Box 41, Folder 1538)
  - Link, James Wilson (Box 41, Folder 1538)
  - Linn, William Alexander (Box 41, Folder 1539)
  - Linsley, James Harvey (Box 41, Folder 1539)
  - Linsley, Ralph (Box 41, Folder 1540)
  - Linsley, Thomas Howard (Box 41, Folder 1540)
  - Lippard, Vernon W. (Box 41, Folder 1540)
  - Lippmann, Walter (Box 41, Folder 1540)
  - Little, William Walker (Box 41, Folder 1541)
  - Livingston, Beverly (Box 41, Folder 1542)
  - Livingston, John H. (Box 41, Folder 1543)
  - Livingston, Philip (Box 41, Folder 1544)
  - Livingston, Stanley, Jr. (Box 41, Folder 1544)
  - Livingston, William (Box 41, Folder 1545)
  - Llewellyn, Karl (Box 41, Folder 1545)
  - Lloyd, Arthur Selden (Box 41, Folder 1545)
  - Lobdell, George Granville, Jr. (Box 41, Folder 1546)
  - Lobdell, George Granville, III (Box 41, Folder 1546)
  - Locke, Cyril D. (Box 41, Folder 1547)
  - Lockhart, Charles Edwin (Box 41, Folder 1547)
  - Lockwood, Arthur Augustus (Box 41, Folder 1547)
  - Lockwood, E. H. (Box 41, Folder 1548)
  - Lockwood, Edward Lewis (Box 41, Folder 1548)
  - Lockwood, John L. (Box 41, Folder 1548)
  - Lockwood, John S. (Box 41, Folder 1549)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box 41, Folder 1549)
  - Loeb, Jacques (Box 41, Folder 1549)
  - Loftus, Charley (Box 42, Folder 1550)
  - Logan, Walter Seth (Box 42, Folder 1551)
  - Lohman, Carl A. (Box 42, Folder 1551)
  - Long, Bert Harry (Box 42, Folder 1551)
  - Long, Cyril N. H. (Box 42, Folder 1551)
  - Long, Henry R. (Box 42, Folder 1552)
  - Long, James McMaster (Box 42, Folder 1552)
  - Long, Theodore Kepner (Box 42, Folder 1553)
  - Longley, William Raymond (Box 42, Folder 1553)
  - Loomis, Bruce (Box 42, Folder 1553)